This might hurt a little.
Sicko is a documentary, comedy, drama film directed by Michael Moore.
A documentary about the corrupt health care system in The United States who's
main goal is to make profit even if it means losing people’s lives.
"The more people you deny health insurance the more money we make" is
the business model for health care providers in America.
Self, played by Michael Moore.
Self, played by Tony Benn.
Self, played by Tucker Albrizzi.
Self, played by Reggie Cervantes.
Self, played by John Graham.
Self, played by Aleida Guevara.
Sicko is a 2007 American political documentary film by filmmaker Michael Moore.
Investigating health care in the United States, the film focuses on the
country's health insurance and the pharmaceutical industry.
Moore compares the for-profit non-universal U.S.
system with the non-profit universal health care systems of
Canada, the United Kingdom, France and Cuba.
Produced on a roughly $9 million budget, Sicko grossed
$25 million theatrically in North America.
This exceeded the official expectation of The Weinstein Company, which had
hoped to be in line with Bowling for Columbine's $22 million U.S.
box office gross.
The film explores themes of corruption,
bureaucracy, cuba, medicine, guantanamo bay.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.